
<P ID="1">Community leaders honored at annual <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> banquet
</P><P ID="2">Story by: <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Jamie Smart</ENAMEX>
</P><P ID="3">Date Published to Web: <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">3/15/2004</TIMEX>
</P><P ID="4">An evening of laughter, surprises and really good desserts sums up the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">2004</TIMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber of Commerce</ENAMEX> annual awards banquet held this <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">past Saturday</TIMEX> <TIMEX TYPE="TIME">night</TIMEX>.   The award winners' families and friends gathered at <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Navarro's Family Center</ENAMEX> to celebrate their well-deserved recognition, as well as an entertaining auction of delectable desserts.   More than <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$1,500</NUMEX> was raised from the highly competitive dessert auction, which preceded the announcement of the outstanding citizen awards.   More than 13 desserts, such as a banana cream pie which sold for <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$150</NUMEX>, and a mango cheesecake, that raised at least <NUMEX TYPE="MONEY">$80</NUMEX>, were offered for auction for the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX> coffers.   While the sold-out crowd of banquet attendees enjoyed their expensive, but tasty desserts, the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX>'s outstanding citizens were presented their awards.   <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">This year</TIMEX>, two <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> senior citizens were honored for their many volunteer community service hours.   "This town's senior citizens are so worthy of recognition, it is hard to pick just one," said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Greg Wells</ENAMEX>, who served as master of ceremonies for the evening's festivities.   <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> described one awardee as <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Community Hospital</ENAMEX>'s goodwill ambassador and the other as a woman who takes her work home with her. Known as the "voice of <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Community Hospital</ENAMEX>," <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mabel Kluth</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">American Red Cross</ENAMEX> and church relief worker Gay Roskamp of the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Christian Reformed Church</ENAMEX> shared the Outstanding Senior Citizen award.   Long-time <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Pioneer Elementary School Principal Stan Davis</ENAMEX> and <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Pioneer Elementary School</ENAMEX> fourth grade teacher <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Rose Hall</ENAMEX> shared the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX>'s Outstanding Educator honor during <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">Saturday</TIMEX>'s banquet.   <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Davis</ENAMEX>, who will retire at the end of the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">2004</TIMEX> school year after 30 years in education, was honored for his ability to be an inspiration to staff and students, alike.   <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Hall</ENAMEX>, who has shaped the minds of area youngsters for more than 40 years, currently teaches 26 "lucky" fourth graders, said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>.   "She makes her students feel as though each is teacher's pet," said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>.   <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">High School</ENAMEX> senior <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Stacey Gorski</ENAMEX>, fresh from claiming grand championship honors at the 49th annual Mid Columbia Regional Science Fair, was named as the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX>'s Outstanding Youth. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> said Gorksi exemplifies the qualities that adults look for in the young leaders of the community.   "She is mature and responsible and manages to balance her many activities with a decent amount of fun," he said.   A familiar face at the <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> city parks, Luigi Rosal, was honored as the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX>'s Outstanding Public Employee. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> called <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Rosal</ENAMEX>, who has worked for the city for the <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">past 25 years</TIMEX>, "the "man of the year for his untiring help with community events."   Honored as the outstanding new business in the community was <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">L&M Screenprinting</ENAMEX>, owned by <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Marietta and Larry Schmid</ENAMEX>. The couple opened their <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> print shop just <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">a year ago</TIMEX>, said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>, who described the husband-wife team as friendly, multi-talented and community spirited.   "They pride themselves on going the extra mile for their customers," he said.   <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> restaurateur <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Jose J. Mora</ENAMEX> of <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">El Conquistador</ENAMEX> was named as the Outstanding Businessperson of the Year. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Mora</ENAMEX>, who arrived in <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Alderwood</ENAMEX> just <TIMEX TYPE="DATE">seven years ago</TIMEX>, operates two restaurants in the community, as well as a mobile vendor wagon, said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>.   "He's in the business of getting down to business," <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> said.   <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Alex de la Cruz</ENAMEX> and wife, <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Audrey</ENAMEX>, were honored for their outstanding community beautification efforts at their brand new A&W/Kentucky Fried Chicken franchise on Yakima Valley Highway.   "The appearance of the couple's building and its landscaping is pleasing to the eye and a real benefit to our community," <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> said.   Long-time farmer Cliff Van Belle was honored as the community's "Outstanding Agri-Businessman of the Year." Van Bell, a native Alderwoodr, farms 1,000 acres of wheat, corn, hay and mint.   "He plays as hard as he works," said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>. "He is passionate about snowmobiling, NASCAR and fishing and water skiing with his grandchildren," <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> said.   Dr. <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">John W. Loffer</ENAMEX> was named the "Outstanding Volunteer of the Year." <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> described <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Loffer</ENAMEX> as a physician who still makes house calls for his elderly patients. He is also the medical director for <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">Lower Valley</ENAMEX> Hospice and the rehabilitation doctor for <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Hillcrest Manor</ENAMEX>.   "He goes way beyond the call of duty," said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>.   "He also volunteers for the school athletic programs and the local Boy Scouts of <ENAMEX TYPE="LOCATION">America</ENAMEX> program," <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX> added.   <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Ruth Barry</ENAMEX> was awarded "Outstanding Health Care" honors for her dedication to nursing education. A clinical instructor at Yakima Valley Community college, "<ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Barry</ENAMEX> exemplifies the excellence we want for all medical personnel," said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Wells</ENAMEX>.   In addition to the awards ceremony, the <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX> hosted a silent auction during the course of the evening, which raised several thousand dollars for ongoing <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX> projects, said <ENAMEX TYPE="PERSON">Tom Gaulke</ENAMEX>, <ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Chamber</ENAMEX> president.
</P>

 




<P ID="5"><ENAMEX TYPE="ORGANIZATION">Webmaster  Copyright Hawk Press Inc.</ENAMEX>, 
</P>

